{
    "questions" : [
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [1~2] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "33_1_img",
            "option_1"      : "① ",
            "option_2"      : "② ",
            "option_3"      : "③ ",
            "option_4"      : "④ ",
            "detail"        : "Man : Honey, how is the location of this painting? Can I hang here.\nWoman : No. Please put down a little bit I think it's a little high.\nMan : Then, around here?",
            "correctAnswer" : "① ",
            "score"         : "3",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [1~2] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "33_2_img",
            "option_1"      : "① ",
            "option_2"      : "② ",
            "option_3"      : "③ ",
            "option_4"      : "④ ",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : It's done. How are you doing Take a look in the mirror.\nWoman : The length is fine and I think the perm is good.",
            "correctAnswer" : "① ",
            "score"         : "3",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [3~6]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 이어 질 수있는 말을 고르십시오",
            "question"      : "3. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  금요일에는 가기 힘들까?",
            "option_2"      : "②  연휴에는 집에서 쉬고 싶어.",
            "option_3"      : "③  근처에 있는 바다로 가면 어때?",
            "option_4"      : "④  친구들하고 같이 여행 다녀왔어.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : It's a holiday from Friday, shall we go on a trip together?\nWoman : good. I wish I could go to a nearby place.\nMan : How about going to the sea nearby?",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  근처에 있는 바다로 가면 어때?",
            "score"         : "3"
        },        
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [3~6]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 이어 질 수있는 말을 고르십시오",
            "question"      : "4. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  우산 가지고 가세요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  제 우산 빌려 드릴게요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  저도 커피숍에 갈 거예요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  커피숍에 두고 온 것 같아요.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Huh? Where did my umbrella go?\nMan : I saw it at the coffee shop earlier....... \nWoman : I think I left it at the coffee shop.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  커피숍에 두고 온 것 같아요.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [3~6]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 이어 질 수있는 말을 고르십시오",
            "question"      : "5. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  지하철이 좀 늦게 왔어요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  기다리게 해서 정말 미안해요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  미안하지만 좀 늦을 것 같아요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  기다리고 있을 테니까 천천히 오세요.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : (phone ringing) Hello. Mr. Sumi? I have already arrived Where are you ?\nWoman : I'm sorry I'm still on the subway, so I'll be there in 10 minutes.\nMan : I'll be waiting for you, so take your time.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  기다리고 있을 테니까 천천히 오세요.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [3~6]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 이어 질 수있는 말을 고르십시오",
            "question"      : "6. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  금방 끝낼 수 있을 거예요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  아직 시작도 못 하셨겠네요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  회의 전까지만 주시면 돼요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  부탁하신 일은 벌써 끝냈어요.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Assistant Manager Kim, is the meeting materials you request going well? \nMan : It's almost over. Should I give it to you now.\nWoman: You just need to give it to me before the meeting.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  회의 전까지만 주시면 돼요.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [7~10] 다음은 무엇에 대한 내용인지 맞는 것을 고르십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "7. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  새 우편번호의 장점",
            "option_2"      : "②  여러 종류의 우편번호",
            "option_3"      : "③  새로 바뀌는 우편번호",
            "option_4"      : "④  우편번호를 쓰는 방법",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Did you hear that the postal code is changing?\nWoman: Is that so? How do you Man : The six-digit number I'm using now is gone and the five-digit number is used.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  새로 바뀌는 우편번호",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [7~10] 다음은 무엇에 대한 내용인지 맞는 것을 고르십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "8. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  뮤지 컬의 예약 과정",
            "option_2"      : "②  뮤지 컬을 싸게 보는 방법",
            "option_3"      : "③  뮤지컬을 고르는 기준",
            "option_4"      : "④  새로 나온 뮤지컬의 소개",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : I haven't been able to watch the musical easily because of the price so far. I have good news for those who like musicals. A package ticket has appeared that allows you to get a discount if you book multiple flights at once. You can choose two musicals you want to see and make a reservation at once.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  뮤지 컬을 싸게 보는 방법",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [7~10] 다음은 무엇에 대한 내용인지 맞는 것을 고르십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "9. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  앵무새 입의 특별한 모양",
            "option_2"      : "②  앵무새와 다른 새의 관계",
            "option_3"      : "③  앵무새가 말을 따라할 수있는 이유",
            "option_4"      : "④  앵무새 소리와 다른 새 소리의 차이",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Parrots easily imitate human words or frequently heard sounds, unlike other birds. Because other birds only move their mouths down, but parrots can move up and down. And unlike other birds, it has a neck structure similar to humans.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  앵무새가 말을 따라할 수있는 이유",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [7~10] 다음은 무엇에 대한 내용인지 맞는 것을 고르십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "10. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  교통정 보안내",
            "option_2"      : "②  사고 예방 안내",
            "option_3"      : "③  차량 수리 안내",
            "option_4"      : "④  고장 신고 안내",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : This is the news I just heard. A car is standing on Namsan-gil due to a breakdown. It's raining, so the processing is being delayed. Currently, the roads around it are very complicated, so there is a traffic jam on the way home from work. Drivers who usually use Namsan-gil should go back to another way.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  교통정 보안내",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [11~13] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 4점)",
            "question"      : "11. (4점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  야외 음악회라서 빈자리가 많다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  남자는 음악회를 꼭 보려고 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  여자는 전에도 야외 음악회를 봤다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  이 음악회에는 인기 가수들이 나온다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Wow, look at the person over there. It's an outdoor concert, so I thought there wouldn't be many people, but there's no place to sit.\nMan : Do I have to see this? The weather is cold and there are a lot of people, so let's go.\nWoman : no How famous are the singers who are appearing today. Besides, it's my first time at an outdoor concert.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  이 음악회에는 인기 가수들이 나온다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [11~13] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 4점)",
            "question"      : "12. (4점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  부산 공항의 날씨가 좋지 않다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 비행기는 서울로 갈 예정이다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  방송이 끝나면 바로 탑승이 시작된다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  승객들은 비행기 안에서 기다려야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I would like to inform the passengers for a moment. Flight HA01 from Busan to Seoul at 5 p.m. will be delayed due to the weather at Seoul Airport. We will depart as soon as the weather at Seoul Airport gets better, so please wait near the boarding gate. We will inform you of the boarding time on the air again. Thank you.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  이 비행기는 서울로 갈 예정이다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [11~13] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 4점)",
            "question"      : "13. (4점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 행사에서는 전통 음식의 재료를 소개한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 행사에서는 전통 음식을 직접 만들 수 있다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  민속촌에서는 농산물을 키워 보는 체험을 한다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  민속촌에서는 사계절 전통 음식을 먹을 수 있다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Jeju Folk Village has an event to make and eat traditional winter food during the winter vacation. In particular, the ingredients of traditional food are agricultural products grown by the residents of Jeju in the folk village. It will be a meaningful event because we try to make traditional food from Jeju Island the old way.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  이 행사에서는 전통 음식을 직접 만들 수 있다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [14~17]다음 대화를 듣고 여자가 어떤 생각을 하고 있는지 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "question"      : "14. (4점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  연필은 자주 깎으면 부러진다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  볼펜은 지워지지 않아서 편하다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  볼펜보다 연필을 쓰는 것이 좋다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  연필보다 볼펜이 부드럽게 써진다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Why do you always use pencils? I'm uncomfortable because the pencil is broken well and I have to cut it often.......\nWoman : I prefer pencils though. You can't erase the ballpoint pen, but you can erase the pencil even after writing it. And I also like the soft feeling when writing.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  볼펜보다 연필을 쓰는 것이 좋다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [14~17]다음 대화를 듣고 여자가 어떤 생각을 하고 있는지 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "question"      : "15. (4점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  극장에서는 여러 영화를 상영해야 한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  작품성이 있는 영화를 많이 봐야 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  요즘은 작품성이 있는 영화가 줄어들었다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  인기 있는 영화를 쉽게 볼 수 있어서 좋다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : I think it's good because many popular movies are shown in movie theaters these days. You can easily see it anywhere.\nWoman : That's right, but people's chances of watching various movies have decreased a lot. If theaters only show the same movie, it's not popular, but it's hard to see a movie with artistic quality.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  극장에서는 여러 영화를 상영해야 한다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [14~17]다음 대화를 듣고 여자가 어떤 생각을 하고 있는지 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "question"      : "16. (4점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  거리에는 쓰레기통이 많이 필요하다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  쓰레기통에 음료수를 버리면 안 된다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  길에 쓰레기를 버리는 사람들이 많다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  쓰레기통이 없으면 거리가 더 깨끗하다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : I can't see the trash cans on the street these days. Even if I try to throw away an empty bottle, I don't know where to throw it away. I don't have a trash can, so I throw it away anywhere, so I think the distance gets dirtier.\nWoman : Is it? I think a little different. I don't have a trash can, so I think the street is cleaner. If there is a trash can, the area around the trash can looks more messy because of the people who just throw away anything.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  쓰레기통이 없으면 거리가 더 깨끗하다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [14~17]다음 대화를 듣고 여자가 어떤 생각을 하고 있는지 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "question"      : "17. (4점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  발표 전에 여유를 가져야 긴장이 풀린다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  청중에게 긴장하는 모습을 보이면 안 된다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  발표하는 동안에는 몸을 움직이는 것이 좋다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  긴장을 풀려면 자신감을 가지고 발표해야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : It's not easy to present confidently without being nervous in front of many people. Professor, is there any good way to overcome the announcement anxiety?\nWomen : It's going to be a long chapter right before the ticket. At this time, 'I can do it well.' It's important to act leisurely with your thoughts. If you take a deep breath two or three times before your presentation, the tension will be reduced. And it’s also helpful to do some body work as you take a step or two before you start talking.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  발표 전에 여유를 가져야 긴장이 풀린다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [18~20] 다음 대화를 듣고 남자가 할 행동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오.",
            "question"      : "18. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  수선비를 낸다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  옷을 입어 본다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  옷을 찾아 간다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  수선을 다시 맡긴다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Sir, here are the clothes you left for repair. Try it on.\nMan : (After a while) But I think it's still a little long.\nWoman : Is that so? It's winter clothes, so I think it wouldn't look good if the sleeves were too short. I'll reduce it a little more if you want. Would you like to leave.\nMan : Yes. I tend to wear the right clothes.( After a while) By the way, can I give you the money when I pick it up later? Woman: please I'll contact you when it's done.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  수선을 다시 맡긴다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [18~20] 다음 대화를 듣고 남자가 할 행동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오.",
            "question"      : "19. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  상품을 산다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  식당에 연락한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  체육관에 간다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  할 일을 정리한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : How are you preparing for tomorrow's sports day? Is there anything I can do?\nWoman : I'm organizing this and that, but there's more work than I thought. I have to go to the gym and bring exercise equipment and buy goods.......\nMan : I'll bring the exercise equipment. By the way, is the lunch restaurant booked?\nWoman: That's done. Then please give me some exercise equipment. I'm going to buy the product right away.\nMan : I got it.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  식당에 연락한다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [18~20] 다음 대화를 듣고 남자가 할 행동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오.",
            "question"      : "20. (3점) ",
            "option_1"      : "①  보고회에 참석한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  출장 갈 준비를 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  보고회 일정표를 준다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  지방 공장에 연락한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : I don't think I can go to the new product report meeting today. I suddenly went on a business trip.\nWoman : Is that so? Why is something going on.\nMan : I called the local factory a while ago, but they asked me to see you because it was urgent.\nWoman : I need to get ready for the business trip as soon as possible. Then how about the new product report?\nMan : So, can you attend the report instead of me?\nWoman : Yes, I will.\nMan : Do you have a schedule for the report? I'll go out first Please check it.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  출장 갈 준비를 한다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [21~22] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "21. 들은 내용으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오. ",
            "option_1"      : "①  남자는 오늘 몸이 좋지 않았다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  여자는 하루에 한 시간씩 음악을 듣는다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  리듬 체조는 음악 선택이 가장 중요하다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  리듬 체조가 이번 대회에서 우승을 했다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : This is the first time a rhythmic gymnast has won a medal. Did you expect to win in advance? Man: I was expecting a little bit because the players were in good condition, but I didn't even think about winning. I just want to thank our players for their hard work.\nWoman : I heard that you gave me special training. I heard that the players listened to music for an hour every day, so why?\nMen : In rhythmic gymnastics, expressiveness is important. That's why I practiced listening to music and expressing that feeling. I think it helped a lot in training.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  리듬 체조가 이번 대회에서 우승을 했다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [21~22] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "22.  남자는 누구인지 고르십시오 ",
            "option_1"      : "①  기자",
            "option_2"      : "②  음악가",
            "option_3"      : "③  체조 선수",
            "option_4"      : "④  체조 감독",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : This is the first time a rhythmic gymnast has won a medal. Did you expect to win in advance? Man: I was expecting a little bit because the players were in good condition, but I didn't even think about winning. I just want to thank our players for their hard work.\nWoman : I heard that you gave me special training. I heard that the players listened to music for an hour every day, so why?\nMen : In rhythmic gymnastics, expressiveness is important. That's why I practiced listening to music and expressing that feeling. I think it helped a lot in training.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  체조 감독",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [23~24] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "23. 남자는 무엇을 하고 있는지 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  다른 서비스와 비교하고 있다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  새로운 서비스를 소개하고 있다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  새 서비스에 대해 질문하고 있다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  서비스를 이용한 느낌을 말하고 있다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : It is said that the Seoul Metropolitan Government will start a new service for passengers who use taxis late at night from next month. I'll listen to the person concerned.\nMan : If you are worried about taking a taxi late, please try this service. You will be able to worry a little less. It's not that difficult to use. All you need to do is register the service on your mobile phone. At this time, you can enter the phone number of a family member or friend to be contacted. Then the taxi number you are riding and the name of the driver will be sent by text so you can prevent dangerous things.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  새로운 서비스를 소개하고 있다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [23~24] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "24. 이 서비스를 시작한 이유를 고르십시오. ",
            "option_1"      : "①  교통사고를 미리 방지하기 위해",
            "option_2"      : "②  불필요한 이동 거리를 줄이기 위해",
            "option_3"      : "③  택시 이용객의 안전을 지키기 위해",
            "option_4"      : "④  휴대 전화를 다양하게 활용하기 위해",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : It is said that the Seoul Metropolitan Government will start a new service for passengers who use taxis late at night from next month. I'll listen to the person concerned.\nMan : If you are worried about taking a taxi late, please try this service. You will be able to worry a little less. It's not that difficult to use. All you need to do is register the service on your mobile phone. At this time, you can enter the phone number of a family member or friend to be contacted. Then the taxi number you are riding and the name of the driver will be sent by text so you can prevent dangerous things.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  택시 이용객의 안전을 지키기 위해",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오.",
            "question"      : "25. 여자의 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오. (4점)",
            "option_1"      : "①  믿음은 일의 효과를 높여 준다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  업무에 적극적인 자세로 임해야 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  대인 관계가 좋은 사람이 업무 능력도 좋다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  상사는 자신감을 가진 직원에게 믿음이 간다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : It's important to trust the other person when you work. Not long ago, I asked 10 office workers what the boss said, 'It's the best word when you work', and the first place said, 'You did a good job. It's you as expected.' It was, and the second place was 'I'm sure you did it.' Showed up with It was all related to faith, and if someone believes in me, 'I'm an important person.' It is said that you will feel it and feel confident. That's why I actively participate in the work. In the end, this attitude will have a positive impact on the work.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  믿음은 일의 효과를 높여 준다.",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오.",
            "question"      : "26. 여자가 제시한 주장의 근거로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (3점)",
            "option_1"      : "①  관련 서적",
            "option_2"      : "②  설문 조사 자료",
            "option_3"      : "③  전문가의 의견",
            "option_4"      : "④  주변 사람의 조언",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : It's important to trust the other person when you work. Not long ago, I asked 10 office workers what the boss said, 'It's the best word when you work', and the first place said, 'You did a good job. It's you as expected.' It was, and the second place was 'I'm sure you did it.' Showed up with It was all related to faith, and if someone believes in me, 'I'm an important person.' It is said that you will feel it and feel confident. That's why I actively participate in the work. In the end, this attitude will have a positive impact on the work.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  설문 조사 자료",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [27~28] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "27. 여자의 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  광고에서는 모델이 중요하다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  광고는 재미있게 만들어야 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  광고 모델은 유명한 사람일수록 좋다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  광고는 상품에 대해 잘 소개해야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : These days, when I'm watching an advertisement, I see the model more than the product. So when the advertisement is over, I remember the model, not the product. I don't think this is in line with the original purpose of the advertisement to introduce the product. It just attracts interest and interest.\nMan : Advertising is done to sell a lot of products. As you said, if that interest ends in the model, it will be a problem. But if that interest naturally leads to an interest in the product, that will also be the effect of the ad. A typical example is that famous celebrities were featured as advertising models and attracted their fans to consumers.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  광고는 상품에 대해 잘 소개해야 한다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [27~28] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 3점)",
            "question"      : "28. 남자의 생각이나 태도로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  여자의 의견에 반대하고 있다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  여자의 주장을 인정하고 있다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  여자의 주장을 무시하고 있다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  여자의 의견에 보충 설명을 하고 있다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : These days, when I'm watching an advertisement, I see the model more than the product. So when the advertisement is over, I remember the model, not the product. I don't think this is in line with the original purpose of the advertisement to introduce the product. It just attracts interest and interest.\nMan : Advertising is done to sell a lot of products. As you said, if that interest ends in the model, it will be a problem. But if that interest naturally leads to an interest in the product, that will also be the effect of the ad. A typical example is that famous celebrities were featured as advertising models and attracted their fans to consumers.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  여자의 의견에 반대하고 있다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [29~30] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오.",
            "question"      : "29. 이 뉴스의 제목으로 가장 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (4점)",
            "option_1"      : "①  식당가,만남의 장으로 활용돼",
            "option_2"      : "②  음식 값으로 이웃 도울 수 있어",
            "option_3"      : "③  장애인 시설,도움의 손길 기다려",
            "option_4"      : "④  한 그릇 값으로 두 사람 먹을 수 있어",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I heard that there are people who pay for food twice at restaurants these days. This news is from reporter Cheol-soo Kim.\nMan : There are people who eat a bowl of bibimbap and calculate the price of two bowls. It is to calculate the price of other people's meals in advance. Anyone can eat pre-determined rice for free when they come to the restaurant. It is also said that it will be delivered to nearby facilities for the disabled. The restaurant serves as a bridge between the person who paid for the meal and the person who eats it. It is said that the number of citizens participating is increasing because the purpose is good and the method is easy.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  음식 값으로 이웃 도울 수 있어",
            "score"         : "4"
        },
        {
            "sections"      : "※ [29~30] 다음 내용을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오.",
            "question"      : "30. 들은 내용으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오. (3점)",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 식당은 식사 전에 계산을 미리 해야 한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 식당에서는 새로운 사람을 만날 기회가 많다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  밥값을 두 번 내는 사람들이 점차 증가하고 있다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  식당은 손님을 대상으로 다양한 이벤트를 진행 중이다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I heard that there are people who pay for food twice at restaurants these days. This news is from reporter Cheol-soo Kim.\nMan : There are people who eat a bowl of bibimbap and calculate the price of two bowls. It is to calculate the price of other people's meals in advance. Anyone can eat pre-determined rice for free when they come to the restaurant. It is also said that it will be delivered to nearby facilities for the disabled. The restaurant serves as a bridge between the person who paid for the meal and the person who eats it. It is said that the number of citizens participating is increasing because the purpose is good and the method is easy.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  밥값을 두 번 내는 사람들이 점차 증가하고 있다.",
            "score"         : "3"
        }
    ]
}
